《绝望主妇》前情回顾
Previously on Desperate Housewives
约翰  你只是个玩物  你和我没有未来的
John, you're a toy. You and me, no future.
有些话一旦说出去
Once some things are said...
还记不记得一周工作60个小时是啥感觉
Remember what it's like to work a 60-hour week?
就收不回来了
...You can't take them back.
没有人比我更想找到黛德丽
No one cares as much about finding Deidre as I do.
-你射伤了自己  -听来挺蠢的是吧
- You shot yourself? - Pretty lame, huh?
后果已经无法挽回
The damage is already done.
妈妈
Mom!
-你不能把她从我身边抢走  -出去
- You're not taking her away from me. - Get out.
你得看点东西
I needed you to see something.
他们说是从麦克的车库偷来的
They said they stole it from Mike's garage.
那是血迹吗
Is that blood?
布里信从传统的价值观
Bree Van de kamp believed in old-fashioned values.
例如对于上帝的崇敬
Things like respect for god,
家庭的重要性
the importance of family,
和对国家的爱
and love of country.
实际上  布里对这些价值观太看重了
In fact, Bree believed so strongly in her values,
所以当她遇见不遵从这些价值观的人时
it was always a shock whenever she was confronted
就会很震惊
with those who didn't.
-不是我的  -你保证过不再出轨了
- It's not mine. - You promised the cheating had stopped.
雷克斯  你保证过的
Rex, You promised.
别大呼小叫的行吗  我今天都快烦死了
Could we not yell at each other? I'm feeling really lousy today.
你给我从家里滚出去
I want you out of the house.
布里  看着我  那不是我的
Bree, look at me. It's not mine.
那是谁的
Well then, whose is it?
它不可能自己跑到我的洗衣篮里吧
It didn't just magically appear in my laundry basket.
这家里又不是只有我一个
I'm not the only guy in this house
用避孕套的男人
that uses that hamper.
-不会吧  -很遗憾
- No! - Sorry.
安德鲁还是个孩子
Andrew's still a child.
他16岁了  这也不奇怪
He's 16. It's not unheard of.
-亲爱的  你得跟他谈谈  -跟他说什么
- Honey, you have to talk to him. - And tell him what?
告诉他我们发现了他的避孕套
Tell him that we found his condom and that
告诉他不许  那啥
he is forbidden from... You know.
我可以跟他讲我们觉得他还太年轻
I can absolutely tell him that we think he's too young,
但这可没什么用
but I don't think it's gonna do any good.
至少我们可以去搜他的屋子
Well, then, the least we can do is to search his room,
如果发现了更多的这个  我们就没收
and if we find any more of these, we'll confiscate them.
那能有什么用呢
That will accomplish what?
如果我们没收了他的避孕套  也许
If we take away his condoms maybe...
他是个十多岁的男孩子
He's a teenage boy.
就算我们把他的小弟弟也没收了
We could take away his penis,
他还是会想要做爱
he'd still try to have sex.
我们不能把这放回他房间
Well, we can't put it back in his room.
那样就好像我们在纵容他进行婚前性行为
That would be like we're condoning pre-marital sex.
布里  我换个方式说
Bree, let me put this another way.
你想不想当奶奶
Do you want to become a grandmother?
没错  布里信从传统的价值观
Yes, Bree believed in old-fashioned values.
但她也相信
But she also believed
做好预防措施比悔恨更重要
it was better to be safe than sorry.
本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 翻译制作
更多字幕下载 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译：   NANA      小坏     破破布      vero     校对：  LIIT
后期：  zwzy_1007(胖胖)       总监：   桃金娘银
■
《绝望的主妇》第一季 第十五集
Desperate Housewives S01E15
郊区的每一个早晨都会迎来
Each new morning in suburbia brings with it
一些新的谎言
a new set of lies.
善意的小谎言  大家认为无伤大雅
Little white lies, told not to hurt...
早啊  派卓夫人  你今天气色真好
Morning, Mrs. Petchul, you look lovely today.
而且能让生活更愉快
...But to make life more pleasant.
人们说这种谎来保护自己
They tell these lies to protect themselves
和他们的名声
and their reputations.
我的天  太让人郁闷了
Oh, for god's sake, this is unbelievable.
我下次坚决不用网上银行了
This is the last time I do my banking online.
当然  有时候
Of course, every now and then,
总有一些人
the day arrives when someone
最终决定要说实话
finally decides to tell the truth.
他被枪击了  你怎么没跟我们说呢
He was shot? How could you not tell us about this?
他挺尴尬的  说这是个意外事故
He was embarrassed. He said it was an accident.
别这么看着我  有时候是会发生意外
Oh, don't look at me like that. Accidents happen.
我们知道你想要信任麦克
We know you want to trust Mike,
但他的车库里有一个死去女人的首饰
But he had a dead woman's jewelry in his garage.
有吗  我们也不能确定啊
Now did he? We don't know that for sure.
我们所知道的只是
All we know is
勒奈特的孩子拿着这玩意出现
that Lynette's kids turned up with it.
也就是说  你觉得是双胞胎杀了玛莎
So what are you saying, that the twins murdered Martha?
我不会排除他们的嫌疑
Well, I wouldn't put it past them.
我是说这跟麦克作案的可能性是一样的
I'm saying that is about as likely as Mike having done it.
他是个好人  我了解他
He's a good guy. I know him.
他  他可是麦克
I mean, he's... He's mike.
我也不觉得是麦克做的
Honestly, I don't think Mike did it either,
但如果我们不报警  就是藏匿证物罪了
But if we don't call, we're guilty of withholding evidence.
说的没错  如果他是无辜的
Well, you know what? If he is innocent, this should
那要澄清不是很容易吗
be a simple matter to clear up.
但是  你想怎么做  我们就怎么做
But... we will do whatever you want us to do.
好吧  报警
Ok, call.
我是不是该直接拨911
Shall I just dial 911?
这又不是紧急事故
It's not really an emergency.
可这是谋杀
There was a murder.
那也不是最近的事了  我可不想妨碍公务
Well, not recently. And I prefer not to tie up the line.
你就打吧
Will you just call?
我妈一会就回来
My mom will be home any minute.
她如果看见你会生气的
She'll freak if she sees you here.
我就是想亲自把这个送过来
Oh, I just wanted to deliver this personally.
我要办一个聚会
I'm having a party.
你知道她不喜欢我们俩见面
You know she doesn't want us to see each other.
你一定得来  我  我是为了你才办的
Well, you gotta come. I... You're the reason I'm doing this.
我会跟我妈说说看  好吧
I'll try to talk to my mom, ok?
但是你真的得走了
But you really gotta go.
-索利斯太太  -抱歉  我认识你吗
- Hey, Mrs. Solis. - I'm sorry. Do I know you?
我是贾斯汀  约翰的室友
Yeah, I'm Justin, John's roommate.
我等了你好长时间了
I've been waiting forever for you to show up.
-是吗  为什么  -我想帮你个忙
- Really? Why? - I want to do you a favor.
帮什么忙
What kind of favor?
约翰说你现在请不起园丁了
John says that you can't exactly afford a gardener right now,
我跟他说我愿意做  不要工钱
and I told him I'd be happy to do it. For free.
你想免费帮我修整草坪
You want to mow my lawn for free?
修整草坪  帮你浇花  修剪灌木
Mow your lawn. Water your flowers. Trim your bushes.
约翰为你做过的事  我都能做
I could do everything John did for you.
你真是善良  不过我看不用了
That's very generous of you, but I don't think so.
为什么
Why?
因为我老公最近一直在家
Because my husband is home quite a lot these days.
如果需要修剪灌木  他可以搞定
If any bush needs trimming, he takes care of it.
这院子真美
This is a beautiful yard.
我肯定它需要格外的关照
I'm sure it could use a little extra attention.
真是受宠若惊  不过不用  谢谢
I'm flattered, but no, thank you.
索利斯太太  求你了
Mrs. Solis, please.
我有没有说过我老公一直在家的原因
Did I mention why my husband's home a lot?
他是被软禁了
He's under house arrest.
他现在对政府非常愤怒
He has a lot of anger toward the government right now,
急需找个人来发泄发泄
and he's just dying to find someone to take it out on.
同志们  这可不是曲棍球场
Hey, guys. This isn't a hockey rink.
你们能出去玩吗
Can you take it outside?
亲爱的  今天怎么样
Hi, honey. How was your day?
我没当成副总裁
I didn't get the V.P. gig.
汤姆  太遗憾了
Oh, Tom, I am so sorry.
我真的想不通
It doesn't make sense to me.
彼得森有事都是来找我的
I'm Peterson's "go-to guy".
蒂姆·杜根在公司就会吹牛
So how does Tim Duggan, the biggest blowhard in the office,
还当上了副总裁  凭什么不是我
get promoted to vice president over me?
我以为你喜欢蒂姆·杜根
I thought you liked Tim Duggan?
我是喜欢  只是  我也不知道
I do. I just... I don't know, I just,
我只是很想升职
I really wanted that promotion.
儿子们  你们能不能到外边去打你们的比赛
Hey, boys, can you please take the Stanley Cup finals outside.
你有没有告诉彼得森你很想要这份工作
Did you tell Mr. Peterson that you wanted the job?
我在那工作了8年半
I have worked at that firm for 8 1/2 years.
杜根还不到两年  我才不会去求他
Duggan's been there for less than two. I am not gonna beg.
我没说去求他
I'm not saying to beg.
你有时候得自己站出来
You just have to step up from time to time.
你得看到机会  抓住机会
You have to see your opportunity and take it.
没人会同情弱者
Nobody respects a shrinking violet.
又不是只能有一种领导风格
There is more than one, you know,  leadership style.
我是低调点  但是很有效率
Mine is quiet but... Effective.
带上你们的球棍出去
Take that racket outside!
你自己喜欢就行了
Whatever works for you.
苏珊
Susan!
美女  去哪了
Hey, sexy. Where you been?
我给你打了两次电话  你在躲我吗
I called you twice. You avoiding me?
我怎么会躲你呢
Don't be silly. Why would I do that?
我就是忙着买杂货而已
No, I've been really busy grocery shopping.
买了两天  你这是在囤货啊
For two days? You must be pretty well stocked.
晚上一块吃晚饭吧
How about dinner tonight?
晚饭  今天
Dinner... Tonight? Um...
你没事吧
You ok?
你能帮我拿一下吗
Can you hold these a sec?
趴在车上
Up against the car!
你有权保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.
你所说的一切都可能
Anything you do say can be used
作为呈堂证供
against you in a court of law.
你有权利雇佣律师
You have the right to consult an attorney...
跟你们说
So get this.
扎克·杨周六晚上要举行泳装派对
Zach Young's throwing a pool party saturday night.
发了一堆正式请柬  用的还是花体字
He sent out a bunch formal invitations.Complete with fancy lettering.
我倒是奇怪他干嘛不洒点须后水上去
I'm surprised he didn't spritz them with aftershave.
请柬做的漂亮不对吗
What is wrong with nice invitations?
妈妈  是泳装派对
Mom, it's a pool party.
他直接在院子里发几张传单就好了
Why couldn't he have just passed out flyers in the quad.
因为他天生就当不了正常人
'Cause he's genetically incapable of being cool.
那你们去吗
So, uh... Are you going?
可能吧
Uh... Maybe.
莉莎和贾斯汀  还有其他几个朋友
I mean, um, Lisa and Justin and some of the guys
觉得游游泳也挺有意思的
thought it'd be fun to swim.
如果真的很无聊的话我们溜掉就是了
We can always bail if it's lame as we think it's going to be..
莉莎是你那个穿了脐环的朋友
Oh, is, um, Lisa your friend with the pierced navel?
是啊
Yeah.
你们最近老在一块玩是吗
You've been spending a lot of time together lately. Haven't you?
差不多吧
I guess.
安德鲁  我希望你周六晚上11点前回家
Oh, uh, Andrew, I'm gonna want you home by 11 on saturday.
11点  周日又不上学
11? Mom, it's not even a school night!
宵禁是没有用的
Bree, a curfew isn't gonna do any good.
你可能愿意放弃
You may be able to abdicate
作为家长的职责
all your parental responsibility,
我可不会
But I cannot.
到底是怎么回事
What... What's going on here?
这是不是跟你放在我房间那个安全套有关
Was this have to do with the condom you left in my room?
事实上  没错  我们得明确一件事
As a matter of fact, it does. And just so we're clear,
如果你让莉莎怀孕了  你就得娶她
if you get Lisa pregnant, you will marry her.
安德鲁  这一点也不搞笑
Andrew, this is not funny.
妈妈  相信我  这很搞笑
Mom, trust me. This is very funny.
主要是因为这个安全套不是我的
Mostly because the condom wasn't mine.
你是个混蛋  知道吗
You suck, you know that?
很明显我们需要谈谈
So obviously we need to talk.
我还是处女  如果你想知道的话
I'm still a virgin, if that's what you want to know.
不错
Well, good.
但你为什么会需要安全套呢
But why on earth would you need a condom?
因为我准备做爱  而且不想怀孕
Because I'm planning on having sex and not want to get pregnant.
丹妮尔  你是禁欲俱乐部的主席
Danielle, you are president of the abstinence club.
我下学期打算卸任了
I wasn't planning on running for a second term.
你打算和谁做爱呢
Who were you planning on having sex with?
约翰
John.
约翰·罗兰  我还以为你把他甩了
John Rowland. I thought you broke up with him.
没有  是他把我甩了
No. He broke up with me.
你知道为什么吗  因为我不想做爱
You want to know why, because I wouldn't do it.
要是他是这种男孩  分了更好
If that's the type of boy he is, then good riddance.
妈  学校里的男孩子都是这种人
Mom, every boy at my school is that type of boy.
而且  约翰不一样
And besides, it's different with John.
我爱他
I love him.
宝贝  靠性来取悦男孩
Sweetheart, just because you give a boy sex
不一定能得到对方的爱
doesn't mean you'll get love in return.
也许我就是犯傻
So maybe I'm being stupid.
那又怎么样呢  只不过是上床而已
What's the big deal? It's just sex.
我在乎你的幸福
I am looking over for your happiness.
我能理解年轻时的那种冲动
I understand what it's like to be young and feel urges.
不过我一直等到结婚  你爸爸也是
But I waited until I got married. As did your father.
那样好得多
And it was so much better.
但是爸爸最终背叛了你
But daddy ended up cheating on you.
是  那个
Yes. Well...
现在他搬回来了  你就更痛苦了
And ever since he moved back, you've been miserable.
你为什么这么说
Why would you say that?
我们卧室间的墙壁像纸一样薄
The walls between our bedrooms are paper thin.
我听到了很多我不该听的
I hear more stuff than I probably should.
妈妈  我很爱你
Look, mom, I love you a lot,
但是你真的是最没资格
But you really are the last person ever
给别人关于性与幸福的建议的人了
to give anyone advice about sex and happiness.
看到这些了吗  又有五份欠费通知了
Have you seen these? Five more past due notices.
别担心  我正在想办法
Don't worry, I'm handling it.
你有什么办法
How are you handling it?
能不能让我先把三明治吃完
Can I please finish my sandwich?
看到我们的银行账户了吗  我们破产了
Have you seen our account? We're broke.
还有按揭要付
We have the mortgage payment coming up...
还有不动产税要交  还有
we have property taxes, we have...
加布  会好起来的
Gaby, it's gonna be ok.
不会  我们真的完蛋了
No, it's not. We are seriously screwed.
而且我很担心你一点都不上心
And I am freaking out that you're not freaking out.
-会好起来的  -什么时候
- Look, things will turn around. - When?
我也不知道
I don't know when.
不过我们是幸运儿  好运会再来
But we're lucky people. And we'll be lucky again.
-那是什么  -割草机
- What is that? - It's the lawn mower.
今天我们有了个新园丁
We got a new gardener today.
不用花一分钱  这孩子是约翰的一个朋友
It won't cost us a cent. The kid's a friend of John's.
-卡洛斯  -他说他可以给免费修整草坪
- Carlos... - And he said he'd do the lawn for free.
难以置信吧  我们是幸运儿
Can you believe it? We are lucky people.
同志们  很高兴又见到你们
Hey, guys, good to see you again.
别那么郁闷  你能得分的
Don't look so glum. You'll get a hit.
不是因为这个
Oh, it's not that.
这个是我"讨厌蒂姆·杜根"的表情
This is my "hating Tim Duggan" look.
杜根又得分了
Oh, Duggan connects.
瞧
There!
瞧这磨洋工的混蛋跑起来那样儿
Look at that job-stealing bastard run.
杜根总是热衷于邀功希宠
Duggan is really showing some of that glory-hounding,
溜须拍马他最擅长不过了
Ass-kissing hustle that he is so well-known for.
我都忘了你在不爽的时候是多么可爱了
I forgot how much fun you are when you're bitter.
他在跑更多的垒
Look, he's stretching for extra bases.
就像他将魔手伸向更多的领域
Just like he stretched for extra territory,
欺负被埋没的全能选手汤姆·斯加沃
screwing over unsung utility player, Tom Scavo.
杜根摔倒了
Oh! Down goes Duggan.
杜根摔倒了  很疼吧
Duggan goes down. That's gotta hurt.
马屁精触杀出局
Oh, Lord! Hound is tagged out, and now he's gonna
看来蒂姆·杜根这一跤摔得不轻
have to deal with some tough dirt stains, that Tim Duggan.
汤姆
Tom...
不  我相信他只是装模作样
No, I'm sure he's just grandstanding.
天哪
Oh, my god!
见鬼
Holy crap!
不过是个游泳池派对而已  大家都会去
It's only a pool party. Everyone is going to be there.
我说不行
I said no.
你想怎么样
What are you goning to do?
难道要让我18岁之前不接触任何男孩
Keep a boy-free zone around me until I'm 18?
一两年内你可以接触男孩  但不要是他
You can see boys, in a couple years, just not that boy.
你为什么讨厌扎克
Why do you hate Zach?
我不是讨厌扎克  就是觉得他有点疯
I don't hate Zach. I just think he's sort of crazy.
人们也说你"有点疯"
Mom, I've heard people call you "sort of crazy".
我是可爱的疯  他是狂暴的疯
Well, I'm adorable crazy. And he's rampage crazy.
-苏珊·梅尔  -什么事
- Susan Mayer? - Yeah?
我是柯普兰警探
I'm detective Copeland,
正在调查玛莎·胡博被杀的案子
investigating the murder of Martha Huber.
我想和你谈谈麦克·德尔非诺的事
I need to talk to you about Mike Delfino.
你记不记得上个月7号见过德尔非诺先生
Do you remember seeing Mr. Delfino on the 7th of last month?
7号很重要吗
Is the 7th important?
我们认为玛莎·胡博是那天晚上被杀的
We believe it was the night that Martha Huber was murdered.
她最后一次露面是那晚9点钟  在杂货店
She was last seen at the grocery store at nine.
她本来第二天约了牙医  但没有去
She didn't show for a dentist appointment the next morning.
-那天星期几  -星期天
- What day was that? - It was a sunday.
天哪  正是那天
Oh! Oh, my god! Yes!
是呀  是呀
Yes! yes!
是   那天晚上我和麦克在一起
Yes, I... I was with Mike that night.
-你确定吗  -是的  我确信
- You're sure? - Yes. I was.
那是个大日子  确定关系的日子
It was a big night, first relationship-wise.
那是我们第一次
It was the first time that we...
-你们第一次什么  -上床
- The first time you...? - Did it.
他们第一次上床
The first time they did it.
-朱莉  -是的
- Julie! - It was.
-你怎么知道的  -我又不傻
- How did you know? - I'm not clueless.
我在洗衣篮里发现了男式底裤
I found men's boxers in the clothes hamper.
别把这写下来
Don't write that down.
很好  你可以放麦克走了  他是无辜的
This is good. You can let Mike go. He is innocent.
假设你说的都是真的
Assuming everything you're telling me is true.
是真的
It's true.
第二天早上她还做了小小的心形烤饼
The next morning she made pancakes in the shape of little hearts.
没开玩笑  小小的心形
Seriously, little hearts.
天哪
Oh, god!
贾斯汀  你在这儿干吗
Justin. What are you doing up here?
我弄完篱笆了
Uh... I finished the hedges.
索利斯先生需不需要我干点别的
Is there anything else Mr. Solis wants done?
我不知道  他不在家  去见律师了
I don't know. He's not here. He had a meeting with his lawyer.
那么这儿就只有我们两个了
So I guess that means we're all alone.
不  就我一个  你该走了
No. That means I'm all alone. You're leaving.
我不着急走
I'm not in a hurry.
我们可以一起待一会儿
Come on, we could hang out for a while.
我不这么想
I don't think so.
别这样  如果你了解我
Come on. If you just got to know me,
你会知道我多有趣
you'd see I can be lots of fun.
我的朋友都这么说
All my friends say so.
我没兴趣和你交朋友
I'm not interested in becoming one of your friends.
滚出我的卧室
Get out of my bedroom.
别这样  索利斯太太  对我好点
Come on, mrs. Solis. Be nice.
这么做可不对
You shouldn't have done that.
你知不知道
Do you know how easy it would be
要告诉我丈夫你图谋不轨是多么容易
for me to tell my husband what you tried to do?
告诉他你和约翰的事儿对我来说更容易
Not as easy as it'd be for me to tell him about you and John.
很抱歉  索利斯太太
I... I'm sorry, Mrs. Solis,
不过你得对我客气点
but you're gonna have to be nice to me,
至少一回
at least once.
麦克
Mike!
麦克  你还好吧
Mike! Are you ok?
是  是  有点儿尴尬
Uh... Yeah. Yeah. I'm a little bit embarrassed.
一定成了邻居们的话题
Must be the talk of the neighborhood.
没有  没有的事
No. Not really. No.
你猜怎么样  我提供了你的不在场证明
So guess what? I'm your alibi.
我跟警方说
I told the police
胡博夫人被杀的那晚我们在一起
that we were together the night Mrs. Huber was killed.
而且那是难忘的一晚
And that I could never forget that night.
你相信我没有杀胡博夫人
You don't think I killed Mrs. Huber?
信  我当然信
No! No, of course not.
我相信你不会杀任何人
I could never think you killed anybody,
即使我没有你的不在场证明  何况我有
even if I wasn't your alibi, which I am.
好  我要去洗个澡
Ok. I'm, um, I'm gonna go take a shower.
监狱环境比较恶劣
Jail's kinda gross.
回头给你电话  好吗
I'll call you later. Ok?
好  什么时候
Sure. When?
稍后吧  我还有些事要处理  好吗
Later. I just got some stuff I gotta take care of. Ok?
好
Ok.
-范德坎普太太  -你好  约翰
- Mrs. Van de kamp. - Hello, John.
不好意思  我不请自来  你有时间吗
I'm sorry to drop by unannounced. Do you have a moment?
当然
Sure.
那么  您来有什么事吗
So... What can I do for you?
是这样  我女儿打算把初夜献给你
Well, I tell you, my daughter is planning on giving you her virginity
如果你肯拒绝她的话  我感激不尽
and I would consider it a personal favor if you wouldn't take it.
蒂姆情况怎么样
So what's the word on Tim?
他的心脏搭桥手术很成功
He came through the triple bypass with flying colors.
感谢上帝
Thank god.
没有那么顺利
It's not all coming up roses.
他得有四个半月
He's not gonna be able to come back
不能回来工作了
to work for four-and-a-half months.
想说什么
What?
公司业务还在扩大
Company still needs to expand,
我想他们需要个健康的敏锐的家伙
I figure that they need a fit, heart-smart guy
像我这样的  走出来收拾局面
like me to step up, take the ball.
你在指望升到他的位置吗
You're going after his promotion?
不  我已经得到了
No. I already got it.
你真该见识一下当时的我
You should have seen me.
我径直走进彼得森的办公室
I walked straight into Peterson's office
跟他说  如果他还是要升杜根的话就太蠢了
and told him he would be a fool to hold Duggan's promotion.
-你说你的老板蠢  -是的
- You called your boss a fool? - I did.
现在想起来真险
That was risky in retrospect.
不过他仍然给了我这职位
But still he gave me the job.
-天啊  太棒了  -亲爱的  是我
- Oh, my god. That's great. - Honey, it's me.
我得到了整个西海岸
I got the whole west coast.
我  什么  什么西海岸
Oh, my... What? What the whole west coast?
我以为你得到是一个内部的职位
I thought you were going after an in-house position.
不是  我将要建立一个新的分公司来负责
No. I'm setting up new offices from
西雅图到洛杉矶地区  我告诉过你的
Seattle to LA. I told you that.
不
No.
不  你没说过
No, you didn't.
好吧  这会导致出差多那么一点  但是
Ok. Well, so it's gonna be a little bit more travel, but...
多一点
More travel?
汤姆  你已经有一半的时间都不在家了
Tom, you're barely here half the time as it is.
现在你还要  什么  双倍工作量吗
Now you're gonna have, what, twice the workload?
亲爱的  别妨碍这事
Honey, please don't ruin this.
你应该跟我商量一下
You should have consulted with me.
我说过  你让我别再像个畏缩不前的胆小鬼
I did! You told me to stop being a shrinking violet.
我以为那就是个内部职位
I thought this was an in-house position.
好吧  我要去洗澡了
Ok, I'm gonna go shower.
等一下  我知道这对你意味着什么
Look, wait. Wait. I know what this means to you.
不  你不知道  你不明白
No, you don't. No, you don't.
我已经41岁了
I am 41 years old.
如果我现在还不能做到副总裁的话
If I don't make vice president now,
那就再也没机会了
it's never gonna happen.
这是我的事业  它对我很重要
This is my career. It's important to me.
我也是啊  但我辞职了  我就没牺牲吗
So was mine. But I'm here, aren't I?
我还是要接受这个职位
I'm gonna take the job.
她说你跟她分手
She said you broke up with her
是因为她拒绝跟你做爱
because she refused to have sex.
好吧  事情是这样的
Wow! um... Ok, here's the deal.
我说过  但这只是个借口
I said that. But it was just an excuse.
我是说  事实是  我不是那么喜欢她
I mean, the truth is, I wasn't that into her.
真的
Really?
而她总是很骄傲自己是处女
She was always so proud of never having done it,
我发现  我可以拿这个做借口
I figured, "hey, this is my way out."
她对你是如此的用情
Well, she feels very passionately about you.
别会错意  她很好
Don't get me wrong. She's nice.
但事实上  我心里有别人
But the truth is, there's someone else.
你们关系确定了吗
Oh, are you going steady?
不算是  我们过去常见面
Not exactly. We were seeing each other pretty regularly,
但那位女士  女孩  把我甩了
but this other lady... Girl, she sort of dumped me.
我明白了
Oh, I see.
我会跟丹妮尔谈谈
Look, I'll talk to Danielle
别担心  我会温柔地跟她做个了断
and don't worry, I'll let her down gently.
其实  我并不希望你那么温柔
Um, actually, I would prefer if you didn't.
我了解我的女儿  她很执着
I know my daughter. She's very determined.
除非你真的对她很决绝
Unless you're really firm with her,
不然她还会抱有幻想的
she'll think there's hope.
好吧  我会很坚决的
Ok. I'll be firm.
最好是残酷一些
Better still, be brutal.
决定沉迷于口舌之快是吗
Decided to indulge your sweet tooth?
我一年之内就会死
I'll be dead inside a year.
我有比腰围更值得担心的事情
I've got bigger things to worry about than my waistline.
他们觉得你杀掉的那个女人是谁
So, who's the woman they think you killed?
玛莎·胡博  好事的老女人
Martha Huber. Local busybody.
我觉得她不是被蓄意谋杀的
I thought her murder was random.
她的首饰出现在你的车库里  这算不算蓄意
Nothing random about her jewelry ending up in your garage.
是你杀了她吗
Did you kill her?
不  有人陷害我
No. Whoever set me up did a good job.
现在警察一直在监视我
The cops are all over me.
你距离真相已经很近了
You're getting close to something.
如果真的很近了  我怎么没看到
If I am close, I don't see it.
人们总会留下线索
People leave trails.
总有一条  将会指向黛德丽
One of those trails will lead to Deidre.
不管是谁陷害了你  他就是知情者
Whoever set you up must know that.
也许是吧  但我要是被关起来就不好办了
Maybe, but I won't be much good to you locked up.
我很有钱  麦克  有钱的好处之一就是
I'm rich, Mike. One of the best things about being rich
确保你不论遇到任何问题  都能全身而退
is the security of knowing you can buy your way out of any problem.
我不会把钱带到我的坟墓里去的
I'm not taking my money to the grave.
我会用它来保你周全的
I'm gonna use it to save your ass.
-索利斯夫人  -你好  贾斯汀
- Mrs. Solis? - Hello, Justin.
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
我来跟你的室友谈谈
I am here to talk to your roommate.
约翰  我以为你们都不说话了
John? I didn't think you guys talked any more.
现在我们有事可谈了  比如说你
Well, now we have something to talk about. You.
-我  -是的
- Me? - Yes.
你居然试图敲诈我让我跟你上床
How you're trying to blackmail me into sleeping with you.
-我想知道他会做何反应  -索利斯夫人
- I wonder how he'll react. - Mrs. Solis...
你觉得他会动粗吗
You think he'll get violent?
-你不能告诉约翰这些  -我可以
- You can't talk to John about that. - Oh, I can.
而我也就这么做  你这个人渣
And I will, you little worthless piece of crap.
听我说  索利斯夫人  我很抱歉
Listen, Mrs. Solis, I'm sorry.
我本来不想敲诈你的
I didn't want to blackmail you.
那你为什么还这么做
Then why did you?
我真的需要跟你上床
I really needed to sleep with you.
-为什么  -因为
- Why? - Because...
我觉得我可能是个同性恋
I think I might be gay.
爸爸  爸爸  爸爸
Daddy! Daddy! Daddy!
怎么了
What's up?
儿子们知道你回家会很晚很晚
The boys knew you wouldn't be home till after, um, bedtime,
所以我们决定要突袭看望下我们的新副总裁
and so we decided to pop in and visit the new V.P.
我终于有了间带窗户的办公室了
Check it out. I finally got an office with a window. Huh?
是啊  这都是为了窗户
Yeah. It's all about the window.
伙计们  谁想来骑椅子
Hey, guys. Hey, who wants chair rides?
-我  我  我  -这条路  我们来喽
- Me! Me! Me! - Out this way. Here we go.
要开始了  小伙子们  准备好了吗
Here we go, guys. Ready?
坐稳了
Hold on.
视察新的办公室来了
Checking out the new executive digs?
你知道的
Oh, you know it.
-我能告诉你个小秘密吗  -好啊
- Can I tell you a little secret? - Sure.
丹本来想晋升蒂姆·杜根
Dan wanted to hold the promotion over for Tim Duggan.
是我劝他把这个职位给汤姆的
And I'm the one that convinced him to give it To tom.
-是吗  -没错
- Really? - Uh-huh.
汤姆简直就是个工作狂
Tom is such a workhorse
而且他又是那么想得到这个职位
and he wanted it so badly.
是啊  他就是那样的
Yeah, he certainly did.
怎么了  难道你对他的晋升不开心吗
What is wrong? Aren't you happy about this promotion?
勒奈特认为最好是跟老板的老婆撒个谎
Lynette realized it was best to lie to the boss's wife...
当然这很好
Well, it's great.
很明显  谢谢
Obviously. Thank you.
倘若她的话不是那么令人信服
...Provided she wasn't too convincing.
当然  我的意思是
Of course, I mean,
我会  一直想着他
I will... miss him being gone all the time.
他会挣回更多的钱
He'll be bringing in more money,
但他会错过孩子们的生日
but he is gonna miss the birthdays,
篮球比赛  第一次的蹒跚学步
baseball games, first steps.
但有得必有失嘛  对吧
But that's the trade-off. Right?
我只是希望汤姆有朝一日回想过去
I just hope one day Tom doesn't look back
不会后悔错过那么多美好时光
and regret being gone so much.
我最好在他们打碎东西之前出去看看
Oh, I better get out there before they break something.
-好的  一会见  -好
- Of course. I will see you soon. - Ok.
你在这种感觉的驱使下做出过什么吗
So, have you been acting on these feelings?
我有个哥们  我们常在一起
I got a buddy. We get together.
胡搞瞎闹的  不过没什么大不了的
Mess around. But it's no big deal.
就是最近  我开始关心他  而且
It's just lately, I've been starting to care about him and...
我不知道该怎么办
and I don't know how to handle it.
我想如果你跟你这样的人上床了
And I thought if I sleep with somebody like you,
我就能有个确定的答案  不用再惊慌了
I'll know for sure and I can stop freaking out about this.
但为什么非得是我  你是个很帅的男孩
But why me? You're a good-looking kid.
为什么不跟你的同龄人试试呢
Why not test drive someone your own age?
女孩们很八卦  如果我开始跟什么人约会
Girls talk. If I start something with somebody
结果最后  搞砸了
and it doesn't... work out,
学校里的每个人就都会发现的
Everyone at school will find out.
而且我觉得我可以信任你
And I figured I can trust you,
你已经有丈夫  有所有一切了
cause you have a husband and all.
从某种诡异的角度上  我能理解你了
Well, I guess that makes sense in a weird sort of way.
你看  我哥们儿和我
You know, my buddy and I have been
在一起有些日子了
messing around for quite a while,
我一直告诉我自己
and this whole time I kept telling myself
这根本不代表什么  你明白吗
that it didn't really mean anything, you know?
我在骗自己  是吧
Guess I've been kidding myself, huh?
我们都不愿意承认一些事情
We're all in denial about something.
但是你最后还是要面对现实
But you're finally facing the truth,
那才是勇敢者的做法
and I think that's sort of brave.
-谢谢  -我该走了
- Thanks. - I should probably go.
还是想让你知道
Uh... Just so you know,
我绝不会告诉索利斯先生你和约翰的事情
I never would have told Mr. Solis about you and John.
我可能是同性恋  但我不是个混蛋
I may be gay but I'm not a jerk.
你有什么感觉吗
Did you feel anything?
没什么感觉
Not really.
你肯定是同性恋
You're definitely gay.
不好意思这么晚打扰你
Hi. I'm sorry to bother you at night,
但我希望你能去警察局
but I was hoping that you could come to the station
再回答我们一些问题
to answer more questions.
现在吗  不好意思
Now? Well, I'm sorry,
我和我女儿今晚要去看电影
my daughter and I were gonna go see a movie tonight.
妈妈  我们可以改天去  没关系
Mom? We can do it another night. I'll be fine.
-等我拿下包  -没问题
- Uh, let me get my purse. - Great.
-你肯定吗  -是的
- Are you sure? - Yeah.
我不会很晚回来的
I won't be late.
-再见  -再见
- Bye. - Bye.
你说麦克7日晚10点
You said that Mike came to your house
去了你家
around 10 p.m. on the night of the seventh.
我是应该对着摄像机说还是
Um, am I supposed to talk into the camera or...
不用  对着我说就可以
No. Just talk to me.
好  没错  他来的时候大概是10点
Ok. Uh, yes. He came over around ten o'clock.
你知道麦克和玛莎·胡博之间
Do you know of any tension, uh,
有什么过节吗
between Mike and Martha Huber?
不知道
No.
你知道麦克最近中了枪伤吗
Were you aware Mike was shot recently?
知道  情人节那天
Yes, on Valentine's Day.
你知道是怎么回事吗
Do you know how that came about?
他擦枪时  枪不慎掉在地上
He dropped his gun, cleaning it.
梅尔太太  我用枪已经很多年了
Ms Mayer, I've been around guns for years.
从没见过枪因掉在地上而走火
I've never seen one discharge when it hits the ground.
必须有人扣动扳机
Someone has to pull the trigger.
那我就不知道了
I wouldn't know about that.
你知道有人在情人节的前一天
Were you aware there was a home invasion
入侵了松树大道上的一户人家吗
on Pine Avenue the day before Valentine's?
不
No.
入侵者腹部中枪
The intruder was shot in the stomach.
麦克的枪伤在哪
Where was Mike's wound?
在腹部
The stomach.
你爱他吗
Do you love him?
什么
What?
这有什么必然联系
What does that have to do with...?
有时  恋爱中的人们会做傻事
Sometimes people do stupid things when they're in love.
我很清楚  我结过4次婚了
I should know. I've been married four times.
告诉我真相  他当晚没跟你在一起吧
Tell me the truth. He wasn't with you that night.
-他求你为他撒谎  -不  他没有
- He asked you to lie for him. - No, he didn't.
他真的跟我在一起  麦克不会杀任何人
He was with me. And Mike wouldn't kill anybody.
这一点我很确定
I'm sure of that.
麦克·德尔非诺  1987年被判刑
Mike Delfino, convicted 1987,
因毒品交易和过失杀人
did five-and-a-half years
入狱5年半
for drug trafficing and manslaughter.
你要咖啡吗  我去喝杯咖啡
You want a coffe? I'm gonna go for a coffe.
她在包庇她的男人吗
Is she covering for her guy?
不  她是被骗了
No. She's just a sucker.
我想泳池里还没人呢  你去游吗
I guess no one's in the pool yet. Are you gonna swim?
拜托  我刚花了一小时吹头发
Please, I just spent an hour blowing out my hair.
祝你好运  伙计
Good luck, man.
我  我们待会见  好吗
I'll... I'll see you later. Ok?
好啊
Ok.
我为你准备了一个惊喜
Hey, I got a surprise for you.
你想去别处谈谈吗
You wanna go somewhere and talk?
好啊  我们是该谈谈
Yeah. We should talk.
你来啦
Hi. You made it.
安德鲁在这儿  没想到他会来
Andrew's here. Didn't think he'd come.
是啊  他带了朋友来
Yeah, he brought his friends.
他们到处惹事  见怪不怪了
They're acting like total jerks. Alert the media.
我无所谓  现在你来了  一切都会好的
I don't care. You're here now. This is gonna be great.
来吧  我们走
Come on, man. Let's go.
-丹妮尔  -别碰我
- Danielle! - Don't touch me!
希望你会游泳
Hope you can swim.
-你们能别折腾了吗  -这多好玩啊  哥们
- Can you possibly take it easy? - It's cool, man.
瞧  他漂起来了
Look, he floats.
放松点  这可是派对啊
All right? Relax. It's a party.
你最喜欢派对了  对吗
You're the main party animal, right?
我说得对吗
Am I right?
应该吧
I guess.
那好  那就要有喜欢的样子
All right! Well, then act like it.
来  学个狼叫
Come on, give me a howl.
你可是主人  投入点  叫一声
Come on. You're the host. Revel in it. Gimme a howl.
这才像话
There you go.
你还好吗
You ok?
我干嘛听他的  他算什么东西
What do I care? He's nothing.
只要我想  我就能收拾得了他
I could take care of him if I wanted to.
你什么意思
How do you mean?
我知道我妈妈的枪藏在哪
I know where my mom kept her gun.
这可不好笑  扎克
That's not funny, Zach.
如果你好好想想  这的确很好笑
If you think about it, yeah, it is.
朱莉
Julie!
丹妮尔  你还好吗
Hey! Danielle, are you ok?
我只是想回家  我们能走吗
I just want to go home. Can we go?
当然
Sure.
朱莉
Julie!
我要送丹妮尔回家
I'm taking Danielle home.
-你会回来吗  -我想不会
- Are you coming back? - I don't think so.
家长会开得怎样
So, how was the P.T.A. Meeting?
很久
Long.
彼得森今天叫我去他办公室了
So, Peterson called me into his office today.
真的
Really?
是啊  他改变了主意
Yeah. He, uh, he changed his mind.
他会替杜根保留那个职位
He's gonna hold that promotion for Duggan.
没关系
Yeah. It's, it's fine.
其实我挺开心的
I'm glad, really.
我也不想花那么多时间工作
I didn't want to work those long hours.
你知道我讨厌坐飞机
And you know how I hate flying.
我的背受不了
It does horrible things to my back.
鉴于这些外部压力
With all that extra stress,
十年后  我的下场就会像蒂姆·杜根一样
I would have ended up like Tim Duggan ten years from now. So...
是啊  当然
Yeah. Of course.
那么  都结束了
So it's... It's over.
有天你会当上副总裁的
You'll make V.P. One of these days.
没关系  真的
It's ok. Honest.
这样的结局  我也很满意
I am, uh... really glad that it worked out this way.
好吧
Ok.
天啊  你吓到我了
Oh, god. You scared me.
最近好吗
How'd it go?
过得挺好
It went just peachy.
又丢脸  又震惊
And humiliating and shocking.
-苏珊  -你怎么能这样
- Susan... - How could you?
天啊  "苏珊  你相信我吗"
God, "Susan, do you trust me?"
"我当然相信"
"Of course I do".
我真是个白痴  你真是个骗子
Oh, I'm such an idiot! And you're such a liar.
显然还是个凶手  毒贩
Oh, and apparently a killer and a drug dealer.
你的阅历不浅啊
That's quite a personal ad you've got going!
-我来紫藤郡  -别说了  麦克
- I came to Wisteria Lane... - Stop, Mike!
别说了
Just stop!
如果你说下去
If you keep talking,
你又会说开我的心门
you're gonna work your way into my heart,
而我不想再让你靠近我的心了
and I just don't want you anywhere near my heart.
永不
Ever.
朱莉
Julie?
妈妈需要一个拥抱
Mommy needs a hug.
朱莉
Julie?
朱莉在里面吗  朱莉·梅尔
Is Julie in there? Julie Mayer?
不知道  里面挺安静的
I don't know. It's pretty dead in there.
朱莉·亚历山德拉·梅尔
Julie Alexandra Mayer!
朱莉  扎克  这太荒唐了
Oh, Julie! Zach, this is ridiculous.
你们不能永远憋着气吧
You can't hold your breath for ever!
你们最好待在下面
You might as well stay under
永远别上来换气
there and never come up for air,
要是上来
'cause when you do,
我就亲手掐死你们
I'm gonna choke the living daylights out of you!
我女儿在下面吗
Is my daughter under there?
我不是  我不是同性恋
I'm not... I'm not gay!
我  我  对不起
Oh... I... Ok. I... I'm sorry.
我就把  就把这个放在这儿
Uh, I'll just... I'm just gonna leave those right there.
我没事  很好  你们就
I'm fine. It's good. You just, you know...
你们看见过   算了  再见
Did you see...? No! Goodbye.
卖掉房子  你疯了吗
Sell the house? Are you crazy?
卡洛斯  我们住不起这里了
Carlos, we can't afford to live here any more.
要是律师能让
If the lawyer gets
司法部解冻了那些账户
the justice department to unfreeze the bank accounts...
那会怎样
Then what? Huh?
我们会有成千上万的诉讼账单
We have tons of legal bills.
即使把我们的积蓄搭进去  我们也完蛋了
And even with our savings, we're screwed.
但是
But...
这是我们的家
It's our house.
我也爱这里  只是
I love this place too. It's just...
我们该面对现实了
It's time for us to face the music.
我从没想过会在人生的这个阶段变成穷人
I never thought I'd be poor at this stage of my life.
卡洛斯  我曾经破产过好几次
You know, Carlos, I've been broke a lot of times in my life.
但我从来没穷过
But I've never been poor.
因为  穷只是一种心态
Because poor is just a state of mind.
现在  你和我只是
And right now, you and I are just...
缺少资金
Without funds?
没错
Exactly.
我们可以找一间公寓  重新来过
I guess we could get an apartment, start over.
也许吧  也许会很好玩的
Who knows? It might even be fun.
一旦我们东山再起
And once we're back on our feet,
我们要买一所跟这一样大的房子
we'll get a house as big as this one.
要更大的
Bigger.
我老婆生日的时候  我送给她那条狗
I get my wife this dog for her birthday.
从收容所领养的
Stray from the pound.
是我送过她的最便宜的礼物了
Cheapest gift I've ever gotten her.
她很喜欢它  我是个天才吧
She loves it. So I'm a genius, right?
后来我发现  它患有奇怪的血液病
Then I find out it's got this weird blood disease.
现在我每个月要花600块买药  我还是天才吗
Now I'm laying out $600 a month for doggie medicine. Am I a genius?
别挖苦自己  你做了好事
Don't be cynical. You did something nice.
你让你妻子很开心
You made your wife happy.
现在我们来谈谈会让你开心的事
Now, let's talk about what's gonna make you happy.
是的  郊区的每一个早晨
Yes, each new day in suburbia
都伴随着一系列新的谎言
brings with it a new set of lies.
最糟糕的  是那些
The worst are the ones we tell
我们在睡前告诉自己的话
ourselves before we fall asleep.
我们在黑暗中轻声告诉自己
We whisper them in the dark,
我们是快乐的
telling ourselves we're happy.
或者  他是快乐的
Or, that he's happy.
我们会改变
That we can change.
或者  他会改变主意
Or that he will change his mind.
我们说服自己  我们能原谅自己的罪过
We persuade ourselves we can live with our sins...
或者  我们没有他也能生活
...Or that we can live without him.
是的  每个入睡前的夜晚
Yes, each night before we fall asleep
我们对自己说谎
we lie to ourselves,
无比急切地希望  清晨来临时
in the desperate, desperate hope, that come morning,
一切都会成真
it will all be true.